Andrew Morgan

andrew@idesignwebsites.co.uk 07599 068379

A seasoned developer with over a decade of experience delivering pragmatic, client-focused solutions. Extensive background in a dynamic agency environment has honed an adaptability to diverse platforms, workflows, and client needs.

I have mainly worked with PHP based frameworks with a particular specialism with WordPress. I have a particular passion for JS reactive frameworks which I introduce to my workflow wherever possible.

Experience

October 2011 - Current role

Mtc Media - Lead Developer

Over 12 years my responsibilities have been varied and include -

- Development in several different platforms including own bespoke solutions
- Scoping and quoting solutions for a range of different budgets
- Point of contact for a wide variety of clients across many sectors
- Key driver of internal development
- · Recruitment and training

January 2004 - October 2011

I Design Websites - Freelance Developer

Created WordPress websites for a number of local businesses on a freelance basis. The clients I had built up during this time were all merged into mtc.when I joined.

August 2007 - September 2008

Paradise Computers

Managed two independent computer repair stores in Arbroath and Montrose. As well as the technical duties of addressing customer issues with software and hardware I had management responsibilities of stocking levels and cash flow as well as introducing a computerised system to both stores.

January 2004 - August 2007

The Computer People

I provided on-site technical support to clients, diagnosing and resolving hardware and software issues.

Education

September 2009- August 2010

Abertay University, Dundee - HND Web Design and Development

September 2008 - July 2009

Dundee College - HNC Computing Studies

References

Euan Johnstone Managing Director euan@mtc.co.uk Craig McCreath
Technical Director
craig@mtc.co.uk